(Penny:)Dr. Plimpton,
I'd like you to meet my colleagues.
(Sheldon:)Dr. Rajesh Koothrappali.
(Sheldon:)-And not-a-doctor Howard Wolowitz.
-Hi.
(Raj:)-I'm a big fan of your work.
-Thank you.
(Sheldon:)And, of course, you've already
introduced yourself to Dr. Hofstadter.
(Leonard:)-Hey, you.
-Hey, you.
(Leonard:)Boy, I'm kind of tuckered out.
(Leonard:)How are you feeling, Elizabeth?
(Elizabeth:)You know what? I am a little tired.
(Elizabeth:)Would you be a dear
and get me a cup of coffee?
(Leonard:)Sure. Black, right?
(Elizabeth:)Actually, now I think I want it
hot, brown and sweet.
(Leonard:)Coming right up.
(Raj:)What?
What do you mean, "what?"
It's "Halo" night.
(Raj:)I can't. I'm too sick.
[COUGHING]
Go away.
(Howard:)That's why we moved
"Halo" night here.
(Howard:)I brought my mom's chicken soup.
(Raj:)I'm not hungry.
ELIZABETH:
Don't send him away. Let him in.
-Who is that?
-I bought a parrot.